when you deploy a contract or creative
当您在混合中部署合同或创意交易时，您会看到字词
transaction in remix you'll see words
like ether and way in account balance
例如以太币和账户余额和交易日志中的方式
and transaction logs what are they in
this video I'll explain what ether is in
这个视频我将解释以太醚方式的一些常见单位中的以太
some common units of ether ether way and
way similar to how the currency of USS
与美元货币在美元内部使用的货币相似的方式
dollar the currency used within the
thorium is ether ether is used to pay
is是醚，醚用于支付大笔交易酬金
block rewards pay for transaction fees
and you can also transfer it between the
您还可以在通道之间传输以太最小单位
channels the smallest unit of ether is
way and one ether is equal to 10 to the
一个醚等于18等于10的方法这是一个完整的台式机单位
18 way here's a complete desktop units
and you can use weights above finis and
您可以使用高于finis和ether的权重来进行固定，但我们将重点放在
ether in solidity but we'll focus on the
more commonly used ones way and ether
更常用的方式和以太让我们来看一个例子
let's go through an example here we have
our contract inside the contract there's
我们的合同在合同内有一个变量设置为另一种方式
a variable set to one way and another
variable set to one either units can
变量设置为一个或两个单位只能在农村数字之后添加
only be added after the rural numbers
for example one liter is about a code
例如，一升是关于代码的，但您也不能写x
but you won't be able to write x either
where X is some number variable
其中X是一些数字变量，将单位附加到a的唯一效果
the only effect of appending a unit to a
number is a multiplication by a power of
数字是乘以10的幂，所以一种方式与乘积相同
10 so one way is the same as multiplying
1 by 10 to the 0 which is simply just 1
从1乘10到0，仅是1升和1升等于将1乘以
and 1 liter is equal to multiplying 1 by
10 to the 18 first compile and deploy
10到18首先编译和部署合同调用函数的一种方法和
the contract call a function one way and
you can see here they returned 1 next
您可以在这里看到他们返回了1个下一个电话，您可以在这里看到
call one either and you can see here
that I returned a big number this number
我返回了一个很大的数字，这个数字应该是10到18，但这有点像
should be 10 to the 18 but it's kind of
tedious to count the number of zeros so
计算零的数量很繁琐，所以我们总是从字面上检查它
we always literally check it for us back
in our code we have a function named
在我们的代码中，我们在函数内部有一个名为test1的函数
test1 either inside this function we
checked that one liter is equal to 10 to
检查一升等于18的10等于10
the 18 way we have already seen that a
way is equal to 1 so this function
way等于1，因此如果一升等于，则此函数返回true
returns true if one liter is equal to
the number 10 to the 18 and returns
10到18的数字，否则在部署的情况下返回false
false otherwise under a deployed
contract hit the test one a third button
合约点击了第三个按钮，该函数返回true，就像我们
and the function returns true just as we
expected gwei stands for gate away and
预期的gwei代表大门，它等于一幢大楼，
it is equal to one building away the
most common situation where you would
最常见的情况是您提交“灰色”一词时
see the word gray is when you submit a
transaction to the blockchain for the
如果您使用灰色来设置交易到区块链的交易
transaction if you gray is used to set
the gas price gas and gas price are the
汽油价格汽油和汽油价格是下一个视频的主题
topics of the next video so for now all
you need to know is that gray is equal
您需要知道的是，灰色等于10亿次，您会看到
to 1 billion way and you see it with
transactions for example open your
例如，交易打开您喜欢的浏览器并访问其中任一扫描
favorite browser and visit either scan
REO and click on any transaction scroll
REO，然后单击任何交易，向下滚动，单击交易明细，然后
down click on the transaction detail and
you can see here that the gas price was
您可以在此处看到汽油价格设置为灰色
set in gray
eaters the currency of ethereum one
食者以太坊一米的货币是10到18方式错误的方式是1
meter is 10 to the 18 way wrong way is 1
billion way and you see often in
十亿的方式，您会经常在交易中看到，我会在下一个见到您
transactions I'll see you in the next
video
视频